<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fernando Contreras</title>
    <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fernando Contreras</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.fercontreras.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.fercontreras.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Me in 10 seconds Software engineer, dancer and writer by hobby
I used to dance break dance, now I´m taking bachata and salsa lessons.
Mexican living in Monterrey, Nuevo León, México.
Me in 1 minute Software engineer with extensive experience in new technologies. Experienced working as consultant and programmer of websites, planning and managing projects from scratch. Always looking for updates on new technologies to provide a good service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.fercontreras.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Mail: fercreek@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Impossible List</title>
      <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/my-impossible-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.fercontreras.com/my-impossible-list/</guid>
      <description> Last Completed Goals  ✅ Have many active incomes ✅ Work for fun, not for money  Current Focuses  Learn about blockchain and finances Improve productivity doing more in less time Invest money in a potential product/business  Fitness/Health Goals  Pull ups - 10 Chin ups - 12 Dips - 15 Bench press  ✅ 135 lbs (November 2019)  Back Squat  ✅ 185 lbs (September 2019) ✅ 225 lbs (November 2019)  Romanian Deadlift  ✅ 225 lbs (September 2019) 260 lbs  BB row  225 lbs  BB Hip thrust  ✅ 155 lbs (September 2019)  Acrobatic  Back flip Side flip Aerial   Dance Goals  Break dance  5 flares Airtrack  ✅ Dance in a salsa choreography (November 2019) ✅ Dance in a hip hop and reggaeton presentation (February 2019) Salsa/Bachata choreography with partner  Professional Goals  ✅ DevOps course by Cero Uno (November 2019) Earn  ✅ 100k MXN in one year ✅ 100k MXN in one year in passive incomes ✅ 1k USD monthly doing trade 5k USD monthly doing trade  Contribute to open source community Get 100 blog visits, all time Be the CTO of a startup  Habit Goals  Read 20 pages a day  Creative Goals  Write a book Play the guitar Learn how to make electronic music Record a guitar song  Skills Goals  Become fluent in English Become fluent in French Become fluent in Italian ✅ Learn Bachata ✅ Learn Salsa  Fun and/or &amp;ldquo;Insane&amp;rdquo; Goals  ✅ Bungee jump Do snorkel Skydiving Surf  Events to attend  ✅ Timbal Latin Dance Congress Mty 2019  Video Game Goals  Finish at 100% Kingdom Hearts Finish at 100% Devil May Cry 5  Travel Goals ✅ Check-in  México  CDMX Toluca Chihuahua Puerto Vallarta Guadalajara Oaxaca Hidalgo Playa del Carmen Mazatlan Los Cabos Zapopan  France, Paris United Kingdom  London Gibraltar  Netherlands, Amsterdam Germany  Berlin Frankfurt  Portugal  Lisboa Oporto  Spain  Barcelona Madrid Oviedo Bilbao Pajares Gijon Galicia Granada Sevilla Malaga León  Belgium  Brussels Bruges  Luxembourg, Luxembourg Czech republic  Prague Náchod  Poland  Warsaw Lublin  Hungary, Budapest Italy  Venice Parma Florence Pisa Rome   To-do Check-in  Zacatecas, Zacatecas León, Guanajuato La Habana, Cuba Las brisas, Huatulco Cali, Colombia  Live for a while in  Poland France Italy  Life Goals  ✅ Have many active incomes ✅ Work for fun, not for money Read 100 books Have a software consulting Be an investor  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.fercontreras.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Nothing to see here&amp;hellip; Move along!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Am Doing Now</title>
      <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.fercontreras.com/now/</guid>
      <description>I´m in Monterrey, Nuevo León, learning about cryptocurrencies, investment, and data analytics.
This is what I spend my time doing:
 Learning about blockchain and investment Writing on my blog Reading books Programming  These are my main priorities right now.
 Be a profitable trader Improving my dialy habits Understand how to delegate and make better decisions on the work Doing more in less time  If my activities or priorities happen to change, I’ll update this page to reflect those changes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>