<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fernando Contreras</title>
    <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fernando Contreras</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.fercontreras.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.fercontreras.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Me in 10 seconds Software engineer, bboy, dancer, and powerbuilder.
I used to dance break dance, now I´m taking bachata and salsa lessons.
Mexican living in Monterrey, Nuevo León, México.
Me in 1 minute Software engineer with extensive experience in new technologies. Experienced working as consultant and programmer of websites, planning and managing projects from scratch. Always looking for updates on new technologies to provide a good service.
I worked as a frontend developer for 2 years, and now I&amp;rsquo;m working as a backend developer until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.fercontreras.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Mail: fercreek@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Impossible List</title>
      <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/my-impossible-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.fercontreras.com/my-impossible-list/</guid>
      <description> Last 5 Completed Goals  ✅ DevOps course by Cero Uno (November 2019) ✅ Danced in a hip hop and reggaeton presentation ✅ BB Back squat 165 lbs ✅ BB Romanian Deadlift 165 lbs ✅ BB Hip thrust 155 lbs  Current Focuses  Gain more muscle mass (How much?) Be a great dancer in bachata and salsa Improve productivity doing more in less time  Fitness/Health Goals  73 Kgs Back Squat 225 lbs Romanian Deadlift 225 lbs BB row 225 lbs Acrobatic  Back flip Side flip Aerial  Aerial dance Break dance  5 flares Airtrack   Professional Goals  Gain 100k in one year Contribute to open source community Get 100 blog visits, all time Be the CTO of a startup  Habit Goals  Read 20 pages a day  Creative Goals  Write a book Play the guitar Learn how to make electronic music Record a guitar song  Skills Goals  Become fluent in English Become fluent in French Become fluent in Italian Learn Bachata Learn Salsa  Fun and/or &amp;ldquo;Insane&amp;rdquo; Goals  Bungee jump Do snorkel  Events to attend  TODO  Video Game Goals  Finish at 100% Kingdom Hearts  Travel Goals  Live for a while in:  Poland France Italy   Life Goals  Read 100 books Have a software consulting Have many active incomes Work for fun, not for money  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.fercontreras.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Nothing to see here&amp;hellip; Move along!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Am Doing Now</title>
      <link>https://blog.fercontreras.com/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.fercontreras.com/now/</guid>
      <description>I´m in Monterrey, Nuevo León, learning to dance bachata and salsa. Improving my knowledge in Ruby, Python, and Golang.
This is what I spend my time doing:
 Power building Taking bachata and salsa lessons Writing on my blog Reading books Eating better and being healthy  These are my main priorities right now.
 Improving my dialy habits Deep understanding of Ruby and Golang Doing more in less time  If my activities or priorities happen to change, I’ll update this page to reflect those changes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>